const STORE = [
	{
        question: 'The number of calories in a Big Mac',
        answer: '540'
    },
    {
        question: 'The height in inches of the tallest man, according to the Guiness World Records',
        answer: '107'
    },
    {
        question: 'In trillions, the GDP of the US in 2019, according to the World Bank',
        answer: '21.4'
    },
    {
        question: 'Number of recognized countries in the world',
        answer: '195'
    },
    {
        question: 'Most points by an NBA player in their career',
        answer: '38,387'
    },
    {
        question: 'Longest field goal in yards for the NFL',
        answer: '64'
    },
    {
        question:"Year that Nintendo became a company",
        answer:"1889"
    },
    {
        question:"The number of years that the Hundred Years War lasted",
        answer:"116"
    },
    {
        question:"The amount of sugar in grams in a 2L bottle of Coca Cola",
        answer:"234"
    },
    {
        question:"Height in inches of Danny Devito",
        answer:"58"
    },
    {
        question:"Height in feet of the Eiffel Tower",
        answer:"1063"
    },
    {
        question:"Height in feet of the Statue of Liberty",
        answer:"305"
    },
    {
        question:"Weight in pounds of the heaviest man ever recorded",
        answer:"1400"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of chapters in the Bible",
        answer:"1189"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of unique words in Green Eggs and Ham",
        answer:"50"
    },
    {
        question:"Distance in air miles between San Francisco and New York City",
        answer:"2572"
    },
    {
        question:"Runtime in minutes of Titanic",
        answer:"194"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of films in The Land Before Time series",
        answer:"14"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of letters in the Khmer (Cambodian) alphabet",
        answer:"74"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of MASH episodes",
        answer:"251"
    },
    {
        question:"Length of world's longest cake, in feet",
        answer:"17388"
    },
    {
        question:"Longest cucumber, in inches",
        answer:"42.1"
    },
    {
        question:"Most total children from one mother",
        answer:"69"
    },
    {
        question:"Most toothpicks stuck into a single beard",
        answer:"3500"
    },
    {
        question:"Height in feet of the Washington Monument",
        answer:"555"
    },
    {
        question:"Oldest codified (contained in a single document) constitution, in years",
        answer:"233"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of elements on periodic table",
        answer:"118"
    },
    {
        question:"In 79 years, how many times does Mars orbit the sun?",
        answer:"42"
    },
    {
        question:"Number of books in the original Goosebumps series",
        answer:"62"
    },
    {
        question:"Population of Vatican City as of 2019",
        answer:"825"
    }
    
];
